Guess it's time,
you better plug in all your nightlights.
What's out there through the attic floor?
Just some laughs, some fun
It's spooky galore!
Why don't you both follow my guidance?
To ensure this month never ends
La
La la
La la la ~
La
La la ~
Come with me
You will be
Ever thankful for my crimes
Against your kind
Find the
hands of all the devils you have brought drag you down
Bring all your friends
To witness genesis
Call till your throat bleeds
Lead them to me
Dance all the night away
Because it'll be your last
Give up your soul just for me
You're not a means to an end
No, you are my playthings
The screams
The gore
And all the chaos
It's all like music to my ears
La
La la
La la la ~
La
La la ~
See my eyes
In the skies
Omnipresent, everywhere
You can not hide.
Children...
Don't you want the spooky month
to last
to last for
to last forev
to last forever?